Finding Aid for Jean C. Crump papers, 1966-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Jean C. Crump papers 1966-2000
Crump, Jean C.
5.5 linear feet
06122 Aa 2
Member of the Ann Arbor League of Women Voters. Election files, 1968-2000, include clippings, informational flyers, meeting minutes and agenda, and voting materials for Ann Arbor primary and general elections; local issues files relate to Ann Arbor minor parties, the presidential primary, and the county medical care facility among other topics.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Jean C. Crump (donor no. 6477 ) and came to the library on August 4, 2006.
The collection is open to research.
Jean C. Crump was a long-time member of the Ann Arbor League of Women Voters (LWV). She served as the League's election chair and as the City of Ann Arbor absentee voter coordinator.
The Jean C. Crump papers is comprised of two series: Election Files and Local Issues. Within the Elections series, the files are ordered chronologically and date from 1968 to 2000. The files contain newspaper clippings, LWV informational flyers, meeting agendas and minutes, notes, and voting materials. The Local Issues series relates to such topics as the county medical care facility, minor parties in Ann Arbor elections, the presidential primary, and punch card voting.
Subjects:
Crump, Jean C.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; Elections--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area.
- Election Files
  - 1968 (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School District, special election (Box 1)
  - 1971
    - Ann Arbor School District, special election (Box 1)
  - 1972
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 1)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 1)
    - General Election, November (Box 1)
  - 1973
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School District, special and regular elections (Box 1)
  - 1974
    - Washtenaw Intermediate School District election (Box 1)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School Board, regular election (Box 1)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 1)
    - General Election, November (Box 1)
  - 1975
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School District, regular election (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School District, special election (Box 1)
  - 1976
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor School District, regular election (Box 1)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 1)
    - General Election, November (Box 1)
    - General Election, candidates (Box 1)
    - General Election, ballot proposals (Box 2)
    - General Election, newspaper clippings (Box 2)
  - 1977
    - Washtenaw Intermediate School District election (Box 2)
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 2)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor School District, regular election (Box 2)
  - 1978
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary and general elections (Box 2)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 2)
    - General Election, November (Box 2)
    - General Election, candidates (Box 2)
    - General Election, miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - 1979
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 2)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor School District, regular election (Box 2)
  - 1980
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 2)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 2)
    - General Election, November (Box 2)
  - 1981
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 2)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 2)
    - Special statewide election, May (Box 2)
  - 1982
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 3)
    - General Election, November (Box 3)
  - 1983
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
  - 1984
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 3)
    - General Election, November (Box 3)
  - 1985
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
  - 1986
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 3)
    - General Election, November (Box 3)
  - 1987
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
  - 1988
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary election (Box 3)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 3)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 3)
    - General Election, November (Box 3)
  - 1989
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary and general elections (Box 3)
    - Special statewide election, November (Box 3)
  - 1990
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 4)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 4)
    - General Election, November (Box 4)
  - 1991
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary and general elections (Box 4)
    - City of Ann Arbor, special election (Box 4)
  - 1992
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election (Box 4)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 4)
    - General Election, November (Box 4)
    - General Election, newspaper clippings (Box 4)
  - 1993
    - City of Ann Arbor, primary and general elections (Box 4)
    - Special statewide election, June (Box 4)
    - City of Ann Arbor, general election, November (Box 4)
  - 1994
    - City of Ann Arbor, special election, March (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor School District election (Box 4)
    - Primary Election, August (Box 4)
    - General Election, November (Box 4)
    - General Election, newspaper clippings (Box 4)
  - 1995
    - General Election, November (Box 4)
- Local Issues
  - Ann Arbor Airport
    - Ann Airport -- Instrument Landing System (ILS) 1972-1991, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - County Medical Care Facility
    - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital, clippings 1966-1971 (Box 5)
    - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital, clippings 1972-1978 (Box 5)
    - Medical care in Washtenaw County, clippings, 1969-1973 (Box 5)
  - Minor Parties
    - City of Ann Arbor v. Richard H. Austin 1971-1974 (Box 5)
    - Clippings 1976-1978 (Box 5)
    - History 1970-1975 (Box 5)
    - History 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Legislation 1975-1978 (Box 5)
  - Political District Maps
    - Information and maps 1974, 1984, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Presidential Primary
    - May 1972 (Box 5)
    - May 1980 (Box 5)
    - March 1992 (Box 5)
    - March 1996 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous 1977-2000 (Box 5)
  - Punch Card Voting
    - Study Committee 1977-1978, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Clippings 1976-1980 (Box 6)
    - Review Committee June-October 1979 (Box 6)